export const questionsArray = [

    {"id": 1, "question": "What is the largest species of eagle?", "answers":[{"text":"Bald Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Golden Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Harpy Eagle","isCorrect":true},{"text":"White-tailed Eagle","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 2, "question": "Which bird is known for its colorful plumage and elaborate courtship dance?", "answers":[{"text":"Peacock","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Flamingo","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hummingbird","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Penguin","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 3, "question": "Which bird is known for its ability to mimic human speech?", "answers":[{"text":"Parrot","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Sparrow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Canary","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Eagle","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 4, "question": "What type of bird is a common symbol of peace?", "answers":[{"text":"Dove","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Crow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Owl","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 5, "question": "Which bird has the largest wingspan?", "answers":[{"text":"Albatross","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Condor","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Bald Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Andean Flamingo","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 6, "question": "Which bird is known for its exceptional migratory abilities?", "answers":[{"text":"Arctic Tern","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Robin","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Penguin","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hawk","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 7, "question": "What bird is famous for its striking red breast?", "answers":[{"text":"Robin","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Cardinal","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Blue Jay","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Goldfinch","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 8, "question": "Which bird is known for its ability to hover in mid-air?", "answers":[{"text":"Hummingbird","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Swan","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Pigeon","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Eagle","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 9, "question": "What bird is known for its distinctive laugh-like call?", "answers":[{"text":"Kookaburra","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Owl","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Crow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hawk","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 10, "question": "Which bird is the largest living bird by height?", "answers":[{"text":"Ostrich","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Emu","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Cassowary","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Rhea","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 11, "question": "Which bird is known for its ability to swim and dive underwater?", "answers":[{"text":"Penguin","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Vulture","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Falcon","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 12, "question": "What is the name of the bird that is known for its incredible speed during flight?", "answers":[{"text":"Peregrine Falcon","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Golden Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Harpy Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hawk","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 13, "question": "Which bird has a bright yellow color and is known for its singing abilities?", "answers":[{"text":"Canary","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Finch","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Sparrow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Warbler","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 14, "question": "Which bird is often associated with wisdom and is featured in mythology?", "answers":[{"text":"Owl","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Crow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hawk","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 15, "question": "What is the name of the bird that is known for building intricate nests out of mud?", "answers":[{"text":"House Sparrow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Swallow","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Robin","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Finch","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 16, "question": "Which bird species is known for its long, curved beak used for feeding on nectar?", "answers":[{"text":"Hummingbird","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Woodpecker","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Sparrow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Crow","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 17, "question": "Which bird is known for its beautiful tail feathers that are often displayed during courtship?", "answers":[{"text":"Peacock","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Pigeon","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Sparrow","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Swallow","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 18, "question": "What bird is often called the 'sea canary' due to its high-pitched call?", "answers":[{"text":"Northern Fulmar","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Gull","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Albatross","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Puffin","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 19, "question": "Which bird species is famous for its elaborate and colorful courtship displays?", "answers":[{"text":"Bird of Paradise","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Peacock","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Flamingo","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Canary","isCorrect":false}]},
    {"id": 20, "question": "Which bird is known for migrating long distances across the globe?", "answers":[{"text":"Arctic Tern","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Peregrine Falcon","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Hummingbird","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Golden Eagle","isCorrect":false}]}
]